Hey. Something just hit the door, didn't it?
Indeed.
Hey, what's going on?
What is that?
M-Monsters?
H-How can they be here?
Enchant Physical Ability!
Go.
Run!
What?
Princess Flora, this way!
These things...
Go.
Crap.
Take that!
These things...
Hey, Yamata no Orochi.
Move.
Spirit Chronicles 2
Roanna, get down!
I'll kill you.
Sir Hiroaki!
I've been wanting to punch this
guy in the face as hard as I could!
That monster... is talking!
You're next. It won't be a peaceful death.
Princess Flora! Please stay back!
You!
Father!
Get out of my way! Let go!
Duke Huguenot!
This isn't nearly all you'll suffer.
Father!
Princess Flora, please run now,
while you can.
What? But... what about you?
I will act as a decoy and buy you some time.
When you see an opening...
hurry toward the hallway.
No, y-you mustn't!
Please.
If things continue like this...
we'll all die.
You! Monster!
Hurry!
Princess Flora? Princess Flora, are you there?
This is Princess Flora.
Please make sure she escapes.
Roanna! Come with me!
Roanna!
Photon Bullet!
Princess Flora.
This way.
Wait!
Let go of me!
Quickly now.
Roanna!
Come now! No stopping, please!
Please move all the way inside.
Haruto.
I sense monsters over there.
What?
Sir Haruto!
Miss Cecilia, and Miss Aishia, too!
I'm glad you're safe!
Yes. We've managed somehow.
I heard that you kept the
monsters at the east gate at bay.
Truly, thank you so much!
Not at all. It was only possible because
of the soldiers and your attendants.
You both must be tired as well.
Let us show you to somewhere safe.
Oh. Before that...
Have any monsters gotten in here?
No.
And we haven't heard any reports of
that from the soldiers on patrol either.
I see.
Are you concerned about something?
Actually, that area there...
It's giving off a strange aura.
That is where the Hero and Princess Flora
have evacuated to. It should be safe.
I'll send word that the area
should be checked, just in case.
Let go! Please, let go of me!
I must call for help!
The monsters in there are
strengthened revenants.
It will be too late by the time help arrives.
Who are you?
Well...
I'm just a piece of human garbage.
Am I what you're after?
Yes. But leaving quietly with
you like this would be boring.
Now, for example, that young lady
who entrusted you to me...
If she learned that you'd been
kidnapped because of her,
I wonder how her face would look.
Even just imagining it is fun.
Yes, that's it. That's the face.
That's very good.
L-Let go of me!
You really are hopeless.
Hey, there.
Stop wasting time. Hurry up and go.
That human-form spirit
has come to the mansion.
Confronting it would present a problem.
Really? All right, then.
If you don't want these
pretty feet getting cut off...
don't make a fuss.
When his interest is piqued, he soon turns
to pursuing pleasure, living for the moment.
He's more of a beast than a man.
Photon Bullet!
We aren't finished here yet!
Huh? Did something just hit me?
Photon Bullet!
No damage at all?
Just how tough are they?
Oh, I'm angry now. Seriously angry.
Sir Hiroaki!
Hitting me with that dirty punch!
You're tougher than I thought.
I hit you with all my strength.
You cockroach.
You die now!
You're a piece of crap!
And frikkin' annoying!
What did you say?
You're next!
Roanna, get down!
I'll kill you!
Die!
Spirit Chronicles 2
Please come this way.
Of course.
What is that?
That's...
That's the room the Hero
and the others are in!
Stop right there!
That's as far as you go.
It isn't likely, but we can't
have you Awakening here, Hero.
Y-You're...
You, go outside. There should be some
interesting prey awaiting you there.
A-All right.
As soon as it becomes excited,
it begins to play.
It is far from being a perfected work.
A defective unit after all.
Hold them back!
Let me go!
Princess Flora!
We'll be taking your princess!
Oh! Roanna... and the Hero!
Someone, please!
I'll cut them off.
That voice...
Catch that man!
Yes, my lady!
Please, stay back!
Aren't there more now than before?
What?
Everyone!
Leave this to us.
Protect the townspeople!
What about Princess Flora?
Haruto, go.
You're worried, aren't you?
Please help Princess Flora.
But...
Right now... your expression
says you're suffering a lot.
Prioritize your own feelings right now.
I'll be all right.
This time, it's my turn to help you!
Earth Prison!
I told you, didn't I?
I can fight too, you know!
Thank you.
Aishia, take care of things here.
Leave it to me.
Lady Liselotte, I promise that I will
rescue Princess Flora and return.
Please, I'm counting on you.
Wh-What was that?
Cecilia, erect magic barriers to protect
those people as well as yourself.
All right.
I will go and reduce their numbers.
Duodectet Magician, Magic Barrier!
She covered areas in all
directions with domes!
And there are so many of them!
Even court mages would
have a difficult time...
Will she be all right?
She's unarmed, isn't she?
She'll be all right.
She's just as strong as Haruto is.
As strong as Sir Haruto?
Enchant Physical Ability!
Let me borrow that.
What?
That spear. Let me borrow it.
Chloe, give it to her.
Y-Yes, my lady!
Here you are!
Thank you.
I'll handle the rest.
Incredible. She really is
as strong as Sir Haruto.
Just who are they really?
Are you certain she's all right?
Let's trust her.
Huh?
That woman... was there back then!
Hey! Don't kill that woman!
I will finish her.
I-It's speaking?
Go.
Enough! I'll do it!
All of you, go after that woman!
Earth Prison!
And now this... will be your end!
Die!
Miss Aishia!
It... can't be.
You're in the way.
Blast it! It can't be!
There's no mistake. That was Lucius.
I've been looking for him all this time.
Where is he?
There should be traces of the
disturbance in the magical energy
from his strengthening magic.
I found him!
Who'd have imagined there'd be
anyone who could catch up to me?
So...
who are you?
Destined Enemy
Next Time
Clash
"Clash."
Spirit Chronicles 2
Sir Hiroaki
Illustration: Minazuki Futago